Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session three of unit six, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet and
scroll down to section three, you'll see
that this is Understand Types of Written
Communications Used in Cyber Security.
There are four learning objectives in
this section and four questions to enable
you to fulfill those learning objectives.
So for question one, this one is asking
you to explain the purpose of written
communications used in cyber security.
So what are the different types
of written communications and
what purpose do they serve?
So think about those, the different ones
that were covered in the course materials,
and what is the purpose of those
communications or those types of document?
For question two, it's an identify
question, so it's asking you to
identify the potential audience
for written communications used.
So as a cyber security person, you
will write reports for different
people or provide documentation for
different people within an organisation.
So you need to think about the
potential audience for those
documents that you are producing.
For question three, it's asking you to
identify the types of information that may
be included in a written communication.
So again, it's an identify, so you
think about what the information that
you would include in there, and again,
think about the audience and what
type of information would you include
that was relevant to that audience?
Then for question four, it's asking you
to give four examples of elements that
support effective written communication.
So there are quite a few mentioned in
the actual course materials, but it's
asking you to give four examples of things
that you can include within your written
communication or what it should have
within there to ensure that, you know,
that written communication is effective
and it can be understood by everybody.
So that's what that
question is asking for.
So once you're happy with all of your
answers, I would carry out a proofread
and then do a full spelling and
grammar check on the whole assessment.
You can then save your unit
six assessment and send that
off to your tutor for marking.